<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>sekvens</title>
    <link href="https://sekvens.buro.earth/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://sekvens.buro.earth" />
    <updated>2024-08-05T17:36:45+02:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>sekvens</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://sekvens.buro.earth</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Merkula</title>
        <author>
            <name>sekvens</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://sekvens.buro.earth/merkula.html"/>
        <id>https://sekvens.buro.earth/merkula.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/13/IMG_20230101_011705.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-08-05T16:28:50+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/13/IMG_20230101_011705.jpg" alt="" />
                    Merkula has played in Odense, Aarhus and Copenhagen. Making music for over 10 years, and 7 years of techno, she is planning to play some new unreleased tracks no one has heard before. Being a part of Odeology, it was only a given the answer was yes to play elsewhere on Funen. Her music as a mix of gritty heavy bangers to hypnotic evolving tracks. soundcloud.com/merkula
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/13/IMG_20230101_011705.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>Merkula has played in Odense, Aarhus and Copenhagen. Making music for over 10 years, and 7 years of techno, she is planning to play some new unreleased tracks no one has heard before. Being a part of Odeology, it was only a given the answer was yes to play elsewhere on Funen. Her music as a mix of gritty heavy bangers to hypnotic evolving tracks.</p>
<p> </p>
<div dir="auto"><a href="https://soundcloud.com/merkula">
<h1 class="glitch" data-text="https://soundcloud.com/merkula">soundcloud.com/merkula</h1>
</a></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Tec2nisk</title>
        <author>
            <name>sekvens</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://sekvens.buro.earth/tec2nisk.html"/>
        <id>https://sekvens.buro.earth/tec2nisk.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/12/artworks-FkzOkLhIytfD2GKz-VHvh7g-t500x500.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-07-31T11:36:56+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/12/artworks-FkzOkLhIytfD2GKz-VHvh7g-t500x500.jpg" alt="" />
                    Tec2nisk (ASTA MARI b2B Louie32) Tec2nisk redefine techno with their track selection and genre fluidity. They distinguish themselves from the mainstream, taking listeners on a captivating and unpredictable journey through the depths of electronic music that is as brutal as it is mesmerizing. Prepare for a fusion of hardcore, acid, trance, breakbeat and electro. soundcloud.com/louie32-0/tec2nisk-b2b-mix-1-louie32-asta-mari
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/12/artworks-FkzOkLhIytfD2GKz-VHvh7g-t500x500.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <div dir="auto">Tec2nisk (ASTA MARI b2B Louie32)</div>
<div dir="auto">Tec2nisk redefine techno with their track selection and genre fluidity. They distinguish themselves from the mainstream, taking listeners on a captivating and unpredictable journey through the depths of electronic music that is as brutal as it is mesmerizing. Prepare for a fusion of hardcore, acid, trance, breakbeat and electro.</div>
<div dir="auto"> </div>
<div dir="auto"><a href="https://soundcloud.com/louie32-0/tec2nisk-b2b-mix-1-louie32-asta-mari">
<h1 class="glitch" data-text="soundcloud.com/louie32-0/tec2nisk-b2b-mix-1-louie32-asta-mari">soundcloud.com/louie32-0/tec2nisk-b2b-mix-1-louie32-asta-mari</h1>
</a></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Matriark</title>
        <author>
            <name>sekvens</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://sekvens.buro.earth/matriark.html"/>
        <id>https://sekvens.buro.earth/matriark.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/11/Matriark_Morten_Bentzon_Main.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-08-05T16:25:13+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/11/Matriark_Morten_Bentzon_Main.jpg" alt="" />
                    Copenhagen-based producer &amp; DJ, Matriark has justifiably earned her spot in the worldwide clubbing scene. Her music productions and DJing energy reflect the 90s and 00s trance era, but also expand the genre with sentimental value additions of the current era. Being a part of the infamous Bunkerbauer collective, a resident at Den Anden Side, one half of duo PLAZA, co-founder of Megatech Industries and a DRIFT Kyiv resident, the Norwegian artist is currently one of the most reliable trance equipment creators around. soundcloud.com/matriarkcph
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/11/Matriark_Morten_Bentzon_Main.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>Copenhagen-based producer &amp; DJ, Matriark has justifiably earned her<br>spot in the worldwide clubbing<br>scene. Her music productions and DJing energy reflect the 90s and 00s<br>trance era, but also expand the genre with sentimental value additions<br>of the current era. Being a part of the infamous Bunkerbauer<br>collective, a resident at Den Anden Side, one half of duo PLAZA,<br>co-founder of Megatech Industries and a DRIFT Kyiv resident, the<br>Norwegian artist is currently one of the most reliable trance<br>equipment creators around.</p>
<div dir="auto"><a href="https://soundcloud.com/matriarkcph">
<h1 class="glitch" data-text="https://soundcloud.com/matriarkcph">soundcloud.com/matriarkcph</h1>
</a></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Eline B</title>
        <author>
            <name>sekvens</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://sekvens.buro.earth/eline-b.html"/>
        <id>https://sekvens.buro.earth/eline-b.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/10/310598568_788654052292089_616943038484441626_n.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-07-31T11:39:11+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/10/310598568_788654052292089_616943038484441626_n.jpg" alt="" />
                    Eline B har i flere år produceret undergrundsarrangementer i Odense. Hun er kendt som initiativtageren til Hulen, Odeology og WATERPLZ. Eline ved, hvad et dansegulv har brug for. Hendes mixes bevæger sig mellem house, disco og techno, men på denne seneste sommernat dedikerer hun sig til techno. mixcloud.com/ElineB89
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/10/310598568_788654052292089_616943038484441626_n.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>Eline B har i flere år produceret undergrundsarrangementer i Odense. Hun er kendt som initiativtageren til Hulen, Odeology og WATERPLZ. Eline ved, hvad et dansegulv har brug for. Hendes mixes bevæger sig mellem house, disco og techno, men på denne seneste sommernat dedikerer hun sig til techno.</p>
<div dir="auto"><a href="https://www.mixcloud.com/ElineB89">
<h1 class="glitch" data-text="https://www.mixcloud.com/ElineB89">mixcloud.com/ElineB89</h1>
</a></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>pace+lead</title>
        <author>
            <name>sekvens</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://sekvens.buro.earth/pacelead.html"/>
        <id>https://sekvens.buro.earth/pacelead.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/9/Kopi-af-pacelead-pic.png" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-07-31T11:43:08+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/9/Kopi-af-pacelead-pic.png" alt="" />
                    pace+lead (he/him) is a sound designer by day and electronic experimentalist at night. He’s been a part of the electronic music scene in Odense for years and is a resident DJ at Odeology and Waterplz as well as co-founder of the latter. pace+lead breathes experimentation and has a borderless approach to genres in his own music. His latest EP-release "Escape" is a five track personal therapeutic flee into a universe of contrasts. A euphoric address where fast and rolling grooves live side by side with weird beats and dark pop with distorted vocals. The entanglement of the sonic entities is an industrial landscape driven by emotional expression. This exploration will be further explored in upcoming releases in 2024. Alien sounds, liquidy atmospheres and sticky grooves should be expected to hit your sensory canal system when he’s to be found behind the decks. The subgenres in his sets can vary from tribal techno to trippy trance and hacker electro but hypnosis is always the driving force of the pace+lead ufo. soundcloud.com/paceandlead
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/9/Kopi-af-pacelead-pic.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>pace+lead (he/him) is a sound designer by day and electronic experimentalist at night. He’s<br>been a part of the electronic music scene in Odense for years and is a resident DJ at<br>Odeology and Waterplz as well as co-founder of the latter.<br>pace+lead breathes experimentation and has a borderless approach to genres in his own<br>music. His latest EP-release "Escape" is a five track personal therapeutic flee into a universe<br>of contrasts. A euphoric address where fast and rolling grooves live side by side with weird<br>beats and dark pop with distorted vocals. The entanglement of the sonic entities is an<br>industrial landscape driven by emotional expression. This exploration will be further explored<br>in upcoming releases in 2024.<br>Alien sounds, liquidy atmospheres and sticky grooves should be expected to hit your<br>sensory canal system when he’s to be found behind the decks. The subgenres in his sets<br>can vary from tribal techno to trippy trance and hacker electro but hypnosis is always the<br>driving force of the pace+lead ufo.</p>
<div dir="auto"><a href="https://soundcloud.com/paceandlead">
<h1 class="glitch" data-text="https://soundcloud.com/paceandlead">soundcloud.com/paceandlead</h1>
</a></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Bilibili</title>
        <author>
            <name>sekvens</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://sekvens.buro.earth/bilibili.html"/>
        <id>https://sekvens.buro.earth/bilibili.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/8/IMG_1299.jpeg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-07-31T11:44:03+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/8/IMG_1299.jpeg" alt="" />
                    BiliBili forkæler dansegulvets folk med en atmosfære af sexy og groovy prog trance og gammel tech house, der presser de +140 bpm. Efter at have pushet musik hele sit liv, har BiliBili fundet et specielt sted i sig for den nostalgiske halvfemser Goa-lyd og nuller UK-tech scene. Dog skal man regne med at blive overrasket med musik fra adskillige andre scener også - især den franske freetek- og Detroit electro scene. soundcloud.com/bilibilixx
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/8/IMG_1299.jpeg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <div dir="auto">BiliBili forkæler dansegulvets folk med en atmosfære af sexy og groovy prog trance og gammel tech house, der presser de +140 bpm. Efter at have pushet musik hele sit liv, har BiliBili fundet et specielt sted i sig for den nostalgiske halvfemser Goa-lyd og nuller UK-tech scene. Dog skal man regne med at blive overrasket med musik fra adskillige andre scener også - især den franske freetek- og Detroit electro scene. </div>
<div dir="auto"><a href="https://soundcloud.com/bilibilixx">
<h1 class="glitch" data-text="https://soundcloud.com/bilibilixx">soundcloud.com/bilibilixx</h1>
</a></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Salti Brothers</title>
        <author>
            <name>sekvens</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://sekvens.buro.earth/salty-brothers.html"/>
        <id>https://sekvens.buro.earth/salty-brothers.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/5/IMG_3508.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-08-05T16:30:04+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/5/IMG_3508.jpg" alt="" />
                    Salti Brothers, Farid (DJ Salty) and Ahmed (Aggi), started DJing together after Ahmed returned from London, where he participated in founding the club FOLD and the record label DIY Records. Salti Brothers specialize in acid, techno, house, electrobreaks and arab-disco. soundcloud.com/ma-hada
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/5/IMG_3508.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>Salti Brothers, Farid (DJ Salty) and Ahmed (Aggi), started DJing together after Ahmed returned from London, where he participated in founding the club FOLD and the record label DIY Records.</p>
<p>Salti Brothers specialize in acid, techno, house, electrobreaks and arab-disco.</p>
<div dir="auto"><a href="https://soundcloud.com/ma-hada">
<h1 class="glitch" data-text="https://soundcloud.com/ma-hada">soundcloud.com/ma-hada</h1>
</a></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>SEKVENS DJ FESTIVAL 30/8-1/9 2024</title>
        <author>
            <name>sekvens</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://sekvens.buro.earth/sekvens.html"/>
        <id>https://sekvens.buro.earth/sekvens.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/BJORNSSON-BUSCK-3.png" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-08-05T17:36:45+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/BJORNSSON-BUSCK-3.png" alt="" />
                    SEKVENS DJ FESTIVAL will be born on the 30st of August in the last summer days of the year 2024. The FESTIVAL is within cycling distance from SVENDBORG (south of Funen, Denmark), and takes place among firs and deciduous trees on Aserbo's beautiful grounds, where there is room for adventure between the viking barns and midieval tower. COCKTAILS – DANCEABLE DJs – BEACH – BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE – TENT PLACE IN SHADY FOREST - MEDIEVAL CASTLE TOWER DANCE FLOOR SEKVENS DJ FESTIVAL is a small, exclusive festival! Follow this page for continuous updates on the DJ line-up, as well as INFO about when ticket sales start. Tickets: Purchase tickets via MobilePay: Choose ticket price: 600kr for all days 350kr for one day Supply your: NAME + SURNAME + EMAIL (example: john doe john@doe.com) in the message field! Send to Mobile Pay box: 2898YQ The payment is your ticket together with the details of the message field. Tickets include dinner and brunch. When you buy a ticket, you also become a member of the association SEKVENS. The festival is for adults only ... and no animals, apart from those already in the forest :-) Location (click image for directions) asmusbusck+sekvensburo@gmail.com Gallery: ARTISTS:
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/BJORNSSON-BUSCK-3.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <div><figure class="post__image post__image--wide"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/449181210_10162321754904883_9096389936249560836_n.jpg" alt="" width="1640" height="856" sizes="(min-width: 920px) 703px, (min-width: 700px) calc(82vw - 35px), calc(100vw - 81px)" srcset="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/responsive/449181210_10162321754904883_9096389936249560836_n-xs.jpg 300w ,https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/responsive/449181210_10162321754904883_9096389936249560836_n-sm.jpg 480w ,https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/responsive/449181210_10162321754904883_9096389936249560836_n-md.jpg 768w ,https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/responsive/449181210_10162321754904883_9096389936249560836_n-lg.jpg 1024w"></figure></div>
<div class="x11i5rnm xat24cr x1mh8g0r x1vvkbs xtlvy1s"><strong>SEKVENS DJ FESTIVAL</strong> will be born on the 30st of August in the last summer days of the year 2024.</div>
<div> </div>
<div class="x11i5rnm xat24cr x1mh8g0r x1vvkbs xtlvy1s">The FESTIVAL is within cycling distance from SVENDBORG (south of Funen, Denmark), and takes place among firs and deciduous trees on Aserbo's beautiful grounds, where there is room for adventure between the viking barns and midieval tower.</div>
<h1 class="glitch" data-text="
    COCKTAILS – DANCEABLE DJs – BEACH – BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE – TENT PLACE IN SHADY FOREST - MEDIEVAL CASTLE TOWER DANCE FLOOR">COCKTAILS – DANCEABLE DJs – BEACH – BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE – TENT PLACE IN SHADY FOREST - MEDIEVAL CASTLE TOWER DANCE FLOOR</h1>
<div> </div>
<div class="x11i5rnm xat24cr x1mh8g0r x1vvkbs xtlvy1s"><strong>SEKVENS DJ FESTIVAL</strong> is a small, exclusive festival!</div>
<div class="x11i5rnm xat24cr x1mh8g0r x1vvkbs xtlvy1s">Follow this page for continuous updates on the <strong>DJ line-up</strong>, as well as <strong>INFO</strong> about when ticket sales start.</div>
<div>
<h1 class="glitch" data-text="
        Tickets:">Tickets:</h1>
</div>
<div>
<div class="x11i5rnm xat24cr x1mh8g0r x1vvkbs xtlvy1s">Purchase tickets via <strong>MobilePay</strong>:</div>
<ol>
<li>Choose ticket price:<br><strong>600kr</strong><em> for all days<br></em><strong>350kr </strong><em>for one day</em></li>
<li>Supply your:<br><span style="color: var(--text-primary-color); font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);"><strong>NAME + SURNAME + EMAIL</strong> <em>(example: john doe <a href="mailto:john@doe.com">john@doe.com</a>)</em><br></span>in the message field!</li>
<li>Send to Mobile Pay box: <strong>2898YQ<br></strong></li>
<li>The payment is your ticket together with the details of the message field.</li>
</ol>
<br><span style="color: var(--text-primary-color); font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">Tickets include dinner and brunch. When you buy a ticket, you also become a member of the association </span><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">SEKVENS.</strong></div>
<div>
<div class="x11i5rnm xat24cr x1mh8g0r x1vvkbs xtlvy1s">The festival is for <strong>adults only </strong>... and <strong>no animals</strong>, apart from those already in the forest :-)</div>
</div>
<h1 class="glitch" data-text="Location (click image for directions)">Location (click image for directions)</h1>
<figure class="post__image"><a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/STNzysWRNmnoozNa8" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/Screenshot_2024-07-30_22-12-12.png" alt="" width="501" height="416" sizes="(min-width: 920px) 703px, (min-width: 700px) calc(82vw - 35px), calc(100vw - 81px)" srcset="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/responsive/Screenshot_2024-07-30_22-12-12-xs.png 300w ,https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/responsive/Screenshot_2024-07-30_22-12-12-sm.png 480w ,https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/responsive/Screenshot_2024-07-30_22-12-12-md.png 768w ,https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/responsive/Screenshot_2024-07-30_22-12-12-lg.png 1024w"></figure></a></p>
<h1 class="glitch" data-text="Timeplan">Timeplan</h1>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://drive.google.com/thumbnail?id=1_di3oSbRkqjRKN_m8zmDvbGTALxcA2hu&amp;sz=w1500" alt="" data-is-external-image="true"></figure>
<h1 class="glitch" data-text="Links">Links</h1>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/dalmosevej-7-5881-sk%C3%A5rup-fyn-danmark/sekvens-dj-festival/435049762675570/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Facebook event</a> </li>
</ul>
<h1 class="glitch" data-text="Big thanks to:">Big thanks to:</h1>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.facebook.com/people/Aserbo/100083508695018/?sk=about" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Aserbo</a> for hosting us</li>
</ul>
<h1 class="glitch" data-text="Contact:">Contact:</h1>
<p><a href="mailto:asmusbusck+sekvensburo@gmail.com">asmusbusck+sekvensburo@gmail.com</a></p>
<h1 class="glitch" data-text="Gallery">Gallery:</h1>
<div class="gallery-wrapper"><div class="gallery"  data-is-empty="false" data-translation="Add images" data-columns="3">
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/gallery/450354288_10162349448164883_566503211513517266_n.jpg" data-size="803x540"><img loading="lazy" src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/gallery/450354288_10162349448164883_566503211513517266_n-thumbnail.jpg" alt="" width="768" height="516"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/gallery/346088034_903651157572094_7332865939428298836_n.jpg" data-size="1440x1080"><img loading="lazy" src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/gallery/346088034_903651157572094_7332865939428298836_n-thumbnail.jpg" alt="" width="768" height="576"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/gallery/426299505_368374035956217_5466683059335685409_n.jpg" data-size="683x1149"><img loading="lazy" src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/gallery/426299505_368374035956217_5466683059335685409_n-thumbnail.jpg" alt="" width="683" height="1149"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/gallery/450463393_461603539966599_6213238735249416536_n.jpg" data-size="1536x2048"><img loading="lazy" src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/gallery/450463393_461603539966599_6213238735249416536_n-thumbnail.jpg" alt="" width="768" height="1024"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/gallery/450463760_461603559966597_1374861039803237294_n.jpg" data-size="1536x2048"><img loading="lazy" src="https://sekvens.buro.earth/media/posts/2/gallery/450463760_461603559966597_1374861039803237294_n-thumbnail.jpg" alt="" width="768" height="1024"></a></figure>
</div></div>
<h1>ARTISTS:</h1>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
